= kissasia.co =
SAY NO TO PIRACY, SUPPORT ORIGINALS
ADAPTED FROM THE EARLY SPRING ON JJWXC.NET
AUTHOR: GU NIANG BIE KU
From next week,
I'll be stationed in Hong Kong, China.
An assignment from my work.
Hong Kong, China?
That's so sudden. You never mentioned it.
The decision was made last week.
Wang Zhiyong got together
with the new intern.
So, you're leaving because of the breakup?
When you're in your twenties,
you think love is everything.
But the reality
will give you a rude awakening.
A five-year relationship
is nothing compared
to the harshness of life.
I will miss Beijing.
But I think it's not that bad.
Perhaps a new environment
could be the beginning of something new.
When I was packing yesterday,
I found this behind the radiator.
RENT A PLACE WITH FLOOR-TO-CEILING WINDOWS
IN CHAOYANG DISTRICT WITHIN FIVE YEARS!
YAO BEI
Isn't it funny?
Come.
A toast to Beijing.
A toast to when we used to think
love can triumph over property prices.
And now, we know by heart
how to use an Excel sheet
to calculate our down payment
and interest.
A toast to Beijing.
A toast to those nights
when we cried and said we couldn't go on.
And when the sun rose,
we still had to save
our presentation slides as a new file.
We learned how to squeeze
into the subway morning rush hour,
and we also learned how to find
our footing amidst the crowd.
INFLUENCER'S PICK, PORK TENDERLOIN 16 YUAN
I want to toast to Beijing too.
To those days
when we cried
and said we wanted
to go home the next day.
Yet when the sun rose,
we swallowed our cold ambition
with a smile.
Shang Zhitao.
You will be fine
because an ambitious person
will not be defeated by life.
We will be invincible.
Come.
AN AMBITIOUS PERSON
WILL NEVER BE DEFEATED BY LIFE
Do you have a history with Luke?
No.
I had to go through a lot to get it.
He didn't ask for anything in return?
He asked me
to do a presentation deck for him.
What for?
I haven't finished it yet.
The automobile company?
Come on.
No need to cover for him.
I already heard his team
has set their eyes on Yueteng Auto.
No wonder he doesn't want Qipai anymore.
You did well. Keep it up.
Go now.
Yueteng…
For the mid-to-low-end customer segment,
you can slightly decrease the budget.
Flora.
You completed the mission impossible.
You are my savior!
But I'm curious.
You managed to impress Luke.
Why did you join us?
I did not impress him.
I couldn't impress him.
Li Tianran, cheer up.
Jealousy is a potion
made with bitter gourd.
It makes your life more bitter.
Regardless, what we want is the result.
Now that we have everything from Qipai,
we can proceed with the rest.
To thank Flora,
the team in charge of Qipai
will have dinner together.
- Sun Yu?
- Hop in.
You…
- Back seat.
- Okay.
- Sit tight.
- Sure.
A COSMIC COINCIDENCE MADE ROMANTIC
Why did you come pick me up today?
Whose car is this? Your company's car?
That's right.
I have been working overtime.
I think I've earned the right
to pick up my friend with my company car.
I'm impressed.
You just got into your new position,
and you got along well with everyone.
A company dinner? Not bad.
Things are picking up right now.
That's good.
Don't. Hide my face.
Let me grab it.
Where are we?
This isn't the right way.
It's not just you.
I also have to pick up Sun as well.
Right.
Pick up Zhu as well.
- Is it cramped back there?
- Very.
I'll get a bigger car
for you guys next time.
How come you're working here today?
My company transferred me
to the self-driving car development team.
They told me
to get a driving license first
so that I could study a driver's habits.
A self-driving car?
Didn't you say you wanted to do that?
This is great.
Driving?
I want to learn how to drive as well.
Sure.
I'll apply through my company.
If you sign up through our company,
you can get a 20% discount.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
Listen. All of you
should get a driving license.
When it's done, all four of us can drive.
The journey of self-improvement
never stops.
That's right. To be more like
the hardworking Tao and the studious Zhu,
I also applied for internal promotion,
so that I can be more like you guys.
I will also work hard
to have a great career.
Good.
Work is tough,
but it also builds character.
Look. Our goals are becoming clearer.
How great is that?
- Come, Mr. Lin.
- Be patient.
Let's wait for Luke.
He's coming as well?
So we'll be talking about…
Have you heard about Yueteng?
As for the Yueteng project, you lost it.
I'm glad Luke managed to win it back.
Don't take this personally
or feel embarrassed.
After all, he gave
Qipai's proposal to you.
We are all one team, aren't we?
Yes.
I've been meaning to thank you in person.
Without your help,
he wouldn't have been this generous.
Not necessarily.
Knowing him, if he truly
didn't want to help you,
he wouldn't have budged,
even if I had leveraged my company
to put pressure on him.
Right.
He always looks down on others
from his pedestal.
Many people in the company
are fed up with his attitude.
But anyway, I did mess up this time.
Luan Nian is a rare talent.
He is capable.
But don't sell yourself short either.
You have your strengths.
This is how Lime works.
We recruit the creme de la creme.
We won't put all our eggs in one basket.
All of you are good at certain things.
That's why our clients
will always come back to us
wherever they go. Right?
Mr. Lin.
Thank you so much.
I am absolutely loyal to you.
I get what you are trying to convey.
I lost Yueteng.
I'm happy for Lime
because he managed to win them back.
If you ever need my assistance
in this project,
I'll drop everything to help out.
Thank you again, Mr. Lin.
Luan Nian, you are here.
Take a seat.
Sorry, Mr. Lin. I'm late.
It's fine. Alex and I
were just talking about Yueteng.
Luke, you sure have avenged me
by winning them back.
My enemy was too weak.
I wasn't talking about you.
I meant the other companies.
It's almost Q4 now,
but they haven't even reached
their KPI for Q2.
While I did get the project back,
I'll need Alex's assistance.
Me? You need my help?
I heard you wined and dined
people from Yueteng's branding department
for nearly six months.
You know their company's
internal project information very well.
- I need that information.
- What are you talking about?
- I…
- Whatever.
Our company needs you two
to work together now.
Yueteng is an important project to Lime.
I hope both of you
can prioritize the company's interest.
Luke, you lead the charge.
Alex, you'll support him.
Is that doable or not?
In all seriousness,
I harbor no hostility.
No one is forever the winner in business.
Today, we are enemies.
Tomorrow, we might be allies.
Alex, your effort is not in vain.
You helped us save a lot of time.
Sincere cooperation
is way too formal for us.
Let's make it simple.
We'll split the spoils.
What do you think?
Interested?
Sure.
Luke will take charge.
Make Lime proud, and I'll also feel proud.
May you bring forth the next miracle run
so that Lime continues
to be the biggest player in the industry.
Come.
Nice.
You did it.
You did well, so you've earned
your place in that team.
- You think so?
- Yes.
Without others' help, what should I do
to be allowed into core projects?
Well, stop making Excel sheets for others
like what you are doing now.
That won't earn you
a spot in core projects.
But by studying the data,
I will be familiar with the projects
and how they function.
I know you love to study,
but results speak the loudest at work.
I feel like I can't think straight
during Spring.
I don't feel like working at all.
Flora. Come.
Flora, you did well this time.
Have you had the chance to thank Luke yet?
Thank you, Luke. I'll buy you coffee.
Flora, you are working for Alex now.
Alex should be the one buying.
It's on me.
Lumi, you sure are quick and witty.
Now that both of us will work on Yueteng,
I trust you'll take charge
when it comes to negotiation.
Working on Yueteng together?
I look forward to working together.
Americano.
Alex.
Thank Luke.
- What is going on?
- We'll talk later.
There's an outsider here.
Both teams working on Yueteng?
- Really?
- No idea.
Ask around.
Hello?
Come in.
My parcel. Yes?
- I have no signal.
- What's…
Miss, do you have a bigger one?
How big do you want?
- Will this work?
- Thank you, miss.
You're welcome.
Is this your parcel?
Come with me.
Do you want us to talk here?
Avoiding me?
Am I a ghost or what?
No, I wasn't.
I'm just worried
that you'd threaten to fire me
without giving me an alternative.
Did I do that?
When you wanted the document from me,
you wouldn't leave me alone.
Once you got it,
you kicked me aside.
I wish to maintain
a professional distance between us.
I can reassure you
that I am not an ungrateful person.
I am very grateful
that you lent me your help.
If you ever need my assistance,
- I'll help out--
- Why would I ever need your assistance?
I am not inferior to others.
If you need me,
I'll do my best to help you,
but please stop threatening me
with dismissal.
I can't bear it.
Shang Zhitao.
You are so timid,
shy, humble, and sheepish.
How can you survive in this industry?
And you said
you were not inferior to others?
I think you're being inappropriate.
Haven't we made it clear?
It was an accident.
Can't you control the feeling of love?
The feeling of love…
can be controlled.
Come here, everyone.
I have a good announcement to make.
Mr. Lin. After you.
I have good news.
Luke managed to win Yueteng Auto back.
Thank you.
Yueteng is our key client this year.
Moving forward, Alex and I
will be assembling a new project team
from both our teams.
I ask for your cooperation.
We only won them back this time
because our opponent, Chengbiao,
picked the wrong printing company.
In the future, we must carefully vet
and pick out the right supplier.
And I want your teams
to submit the list of suppliers to me.
We will go through them together.
Of course, you may also
recommend any suppliers.
Alex.
Anything you'd like to add?
Nothing. We'll follow you.
Luke, you never let us down.
And Alex, you are also a great leader.
It puts my mind at ease that both of you
are running Lime China.
Zhang Ling. Are you out of your mind?
You kept those people entertained
for three months
before you got that information.
And now, you're giving them to Luan Nian?
It was Mr. Lin's decision.
Besides, we took his project, didn't we?
We're even now.
Mr. Lin only sees Luan Nian.
No matter what we've done
or how well we've done,
he never acknowledges it.
Luan Nian never lets anyone down?
Oh, and you're a great leader too.
So tell me, great leader,
what do we do next?
Help Luan Nian achieve his ambition?
Come on. It's not that bad.
Listen.
Luan Nian is not a friend.
When he gets promoted, you'll regret it.
There's an update.
Yueteng wants to change
its marketing strategy
to digital marketing.
I need the data of major suppliers.
Who can do it?
In our line of work, there isn't
a standardized database.
Just because it's the status quo
doesn't mean it's right.
We all have different suppliers
because we work on different projects.
Then, tell me.
Among your suppliers,
who is the most competent?
Who is the most cooperative?
Who can advance us the longest?
What is the maximum amount?
What is their respective expertise?
Who can do it?
I can do it.
But I need someone
who is good at Excel to assist me.
I… I can assist you.
Okay. You'll do it.
On top of compiling the list
of major suppliers, we can include
new suppliers with potential.
Compile everything
and put it in the database.
Our management needs
to be professional and systematic.
Only a systematic method
can lead us in the right direction
and prevent some financial problems.
Of course.
Let's all work together.
Luke wants us to quantify the maximum
advance period and company reputation
into a grading scheme.
That will expedite
the subsequent operation.
Our Business Division has changed
four supplier systems within three years.
In the end, they become scrap paper.
The major suppliers in the market
are not lacking in work,
and the Yueteng project
is on a tight deadline.
Instead of cutting down
the turnaround time,
we have to come up
with a supplier database.
Foolish.
If you want to be foolhardy, be my guest.
I have work to do.
Go to Li Tianran if you need help.
Flora, perhaps you can get clearance
from IT first?
Do you have access to confidential data?
I was too reckless
in the meeting just now.
I was too focused
on bringing you on board.
This task is tough.
I have already experienced it firsthand.
But I agree with Luke.
The market needs fairness and a system.
I'm familiar with analytics.
I can make the supplier database.
I see you've learned
a lot as the Excel sheet girl.
I bet your knowledge of Excel sheets
is among the top five in our company.
And the top four
are those geniuses in business analysis.
I just think knowing it
makes me more efficient.
And you are right.
You know what?
I'll compile the data on suppliers.
I'm not afraid of anything.
If they don't cooperate,
I'll spit on them.
And you…
Go to Luke and ask what he truly wants.
I…
Me?
What's there to be afraid of?
You're working for him.
What is he going to do? Eat you?
He's very serious when it comes to work.
He won't make things difficult for you.
Okay?
Come in.
Luke.
Are you busy?
Yes.
Busy avoiding rumors.
I need to ask you something.
Don't close the door.
Speak.
You mentioned making
a supplier database today.
What is the aim of this exercise?
To build an internal
grading scheme for good suppliers.
Engagement and termination
of suppliers need a system.
Just like when you were studying.
There's a passing grade.
There's a grade for resitting.
When you fall below a certain grade,
you will be expelled.
We cannot be leashed by suppliers.
Our clients all need major suppliers.
If the major suppliers
do not work with us for the evaluation,
we'll make one.
I don't quite follow.
Identify suppliers with good potential
and tell them that I can help them
expand their business
by acquiring smaller companies.
Once the Yueteng project concludes,
they will naturally be the top supplier.
I see.
The market needs fairness.
Big companies need checks and balances.
Small companies need opportunities.
It is a monumental task.
If you join us, you won't be able
to join other projects for a while,
and you'll cross a lot of people.
- You can choose to--
- Worry not.
It will be done.
Okay.
Come to me if you have any questions.
I would like to apply
for clearance from IT.
I do not have access to confidential data.
Submit the application,
and I'll approve it.
Thanks, Luke.
Flora.
You're bolder than I imagined.
And smarter too.
I will continue to work hard.
You can have this. Thank you, Luke.
Sun Yu.
I have to verify
supplier qualifications today.
- I'll be back late.
- Okay. Got it.
TIANTONGYUAN STATION SUBWAY SCHEDULE
CHINA LIFE - CP CENTER
SERVICE QUALITY CERTIFICATION
A HIGH DEGREE OF SIMILARITY
IS OBSERVED ACROSS CREATIVE PROPOSALS
OVERALL SCORE 8.3/10
SUPPLIER GRADING SCHEME HEADER
Tao. What happened to your foot?
I'm such a rookie
when it comes to on-the-ground surveys.
My high heels gave me blisters.
- I'm fine.
- Why didn't you wear sneakers?
Tell them you work at Lime.
You look good in anything.
I'll be more mindful next time.
How did the survey go?
I went to many places today.
Less than half got the passing grade.
He truly made the right call.
At this point, just go back and rest.
I'll go back later.
I have a senior, and I got the supplier
grading scheme header from her company.
I'll sort and organize it later.
It's good to work hard,
but don't overwork yourself.
Go home early.
SUPPLIER GRADING SCHEME HEADER
LIST OF SUPPLIERS
If talented people already work this hard,
I have to work harder to keep up.
LUAN NIAN
It'll rain soon.
Let me drive you home.
Thanks. But I haven't finished
my work yet. Just go first.
Kicking me aside again?
I'm waiting for you at the parking lot.
LIST OF SUPPLIERS
What happened to your foot?
I didn't wear comfortable shoes today.
You didn't wear something comfortable
to conduct surveys?
I'll be mindful next time.
- How is the list going?
- Still compiling it.
Go to HR tomorrow
and apply for overtime pay.
Submit it online,
and put me down as the approver.
I can get overtime pay?
Is that a surprise?
What is the rate?
Per second.
You actually believed me?
Yeah.
Oh, Luke. I have a question.
How come no one
has made this database before?
Can I offset the tuition fee
with your overtime pay?
I'll ask you again tomorrow.
The fiercer the competition is,
the more profitable it is.
The first one always gets
the biggest slice of the cake,
while the rest get crumbs.
A strict yardstick is mandatory
for future systematic management.
I see.
SUN YUANZHU
Hello?
It's going to rain tonight.
- I'll pick you up.
- No need.
I'm on my way home.
Thank you, Luke. I've troubled you again.
I'll walk you up.
I can do it myself.
Thank you.
Tao.
You're here.
Didn't I tell you no need to pick me up?
But the road conditions
might be bad when it rains.
I'm coming over.
Don't get wet in the rain.
- You'll catch a cold.
- Okay.
Thanks, Luke. We'll be going now.
Come.
What's with your foot?
- The new shoes hurt my feet.
- Does it hurt?
Careful.
Can't you control the feeling of love?
The feeling of love…
can be controlled.
Hello?
Son.
Ms. Liu has arranged
for you to meet that girl.
Does Friday night work for you?
Tell Ms. Liu there's no need
to arrange the meeting.
What?
Didn't you just say you would meet her?
What happened?
What I said just now was just
for the moment. Now it's different.
You…
You know I never like
to meddle in your private life.
The reason we arranged
this blind date for you
is that it's hard to refuse such
a kind offer from friends and relatives.
Ms. Liu doesn't know
that you have a bad temper
and a weird personality.
She loves your pretty face, that's all.
Anyway, it's okay
if you don't want to meet her.
That will tell her
how intolerable you are.
Even if you date her,
I'm sure she can't put up
with you for more than a few days.
Let's not waste her favor
and hurt the girl.
What's so funny?
- I have a question.
- Go ahead.
Am I intolerable?
What do you think?
Other than your mom or your few friends,
who can tolerate your antics?
I thought you didn't want love.
Look at you.
Did you confess
to someone and get rejected?
Girls nowadays don't care
about casual flings.
They want to be independent.
They want a career, not a relationship.
I beg to differ.
I think Ms. Shang is quite special to you.
She broke the window with her bare hands
to save you on that stormy night.
Has she ever asked for any compensation?
She fixed your typewriter.
Isn't that genuine kindness?
Everyone wants romantic love.
Unless they are an idiot.
What she doesn't like is the way you think
money can solve everything.
That's not a good attitude.
We express ourselves differently.
Besides, wasn't it your idea
to buy her a gift?
I told you to water a plant,
not drown it with hot water.
I told you to buy her a gift
to show some gratitude.
You made it look like
you were compensating for her loss.
You might as well treat her to malatang.
You are a typical case
of wanting something but being scared.
You don't want her to cling to you,
yet you are afraid
that she doesn't care about you.
Mr. Luan,
you have lost it.
SUN YUANZHU
Hi, hello?
It's going to rain tonight.
- I'll pick you up.
- No need.
I'm on my way home.
- Bye.
DR. LIANG
Mom.
Ms. Liu has arranged
for you to meet that girl.
When are you going to be free?
Listen.
I don't care if you date her or not.
We just have to return the courtesy.
Just meet her once
and don't humiliate her.
A blind date?
I'm free this week. Just let me know when.
Really? Sure.
I'll arrange for it then.
Bye.
Have you been on a blind date?
No.
I think it's great. You can find
someone of your social standing.
It's safer.